streamyx.com 2012-10-03

# Your Privacy

Your Privacy
This page explains our privacy policy which includes the use and protection of
personal information submitted by visitors.
What Personal Information Do We Collect?
If you choose to register and transact using our Portal, you will be required to
provide your [name, identification card number, mailing address, phone
number(s), email address(es), contact preferences], and where you intend to
use the Portal for purposes of making transactions involving online payments,
your credit card information will also be collected for the purpose of processing
your payments. All personal information which you are required for registration
of use of our Portal will be the only personal information required and we will
not require you to provide any other personal information in excess of what is
already provided during the registration process.
You will also be required to explicitly provide your consent to the provision of
your personal information aforementioned in the form and manner as indicated
in the registration process, failing which you will not be able to register and use
our Portal.
How We Use Your Personal Information?
Your personal information will be used for processing for all related services
and analysis to provide services to you. Further, we will process your personal
information for the following purposes:-
       assessing your application or continued provisioning of the services
        provided herein (whichever is applicable);
       customizing advertisements and content on the website(s) and the sites
        of TM and its group of companies (for further information on the TM’s
        group of companies, please visit www.tm.com.my);
       responding to your enquiries;
       research purposes including historical and statistical purposes;
       general operation and maintenance of the services or goods provided
        herein including audit and its related website(s);
       verification purposes;
       matching any data held by TM or its group of companies relating to you
        from time to time;
       provide you with regular communications from TM relating to the
        services or goods provided herein; and
       investigation of complaints, suspected suspicious transactions and
        research for service or goods improvement.
By submitting your information to TM, you consent and authorise TM obtaining
and verifying any information about you which TM may require in connection
with your application for any of TM’s services and/or review of the existing
account with TM from any third party, especially credit bureau or reference
agencies. Such consent and authorization herein will extend to any information
obtained from any of the account(s) presently maintained for you, any new
application for any form of services rendered or goods provided by TM, such
historical financial or credit records, data or information whether or not provided
personally or by any other sources relating to you which was collected,
gathered, received, captured, compiled, secured and/or obtained by TM
through or by whatever means or methods or forms.

Disclosure of Your Personal Information
If you choose to register and transact using our Portal your personal
information may be shared where necessary and only on a need to know basis
with other TM subsidiary or agencies so as to serve you in the most efficient
and effective manner. An example might be in terms of resolving or addressing
complaints that require escalation to other TM Subsidiary or agencies. TM may
disclose your personal information to the following parties for the purposes
stated above:-
       TM’s service providers or agents who are involved in providing the
        services or goods provided herein;
       third parties (including those overseas) who provide data processing
        services;
       any credit reference agencies or, in the event of default, any debt
        collection agencies;
       any person, who is under a duty of confidentiality to which has
        undertaken to keep such data confidential, which TM has engaged to
        fulfil its obligations to you; and
       any actual or proposed assignee, transferee, participant or sub-
        participant of TM’s rights or business.
Your personal information will not be disclosed to any unauthorized third party.
Your personal information may be disclosed due to reasons of law, legal
process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities
and any disclosure will be to such public and governmental authorities only. We
may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of
national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance,
disclosure is necessary or appropriate
Integrity and Access to Your Own Personal Information
You will be able to access your own personal information via your [profile] page
and ensure that your personal information and preferences are accurate,
complete and up-to-date. Any modification to your personal information can
only be done by you. For any of your personal information which cannot be
directly rectified from the via your [profile] page, you may request that we
correct such information if it is incorrect/inaccurate or to delete it if it is no
longer applicable or not required for us to retain such information.
However, we reserve the right to decline to process requests which jeopardize
the security and privacy of the personal information of others as well as
requests which are impractical or not made in good faith.
Where you elect to limit TM’s right to process your personal information, you
may contact TM Contact Centre or visit the nearest TM Point.
Retention of Your Personal Information
Your personal information will be retained by us only for the period necessary
for the purposes of [providing you the services and subscriptions which you
have subscribed] as well as for transactions made by you via the Portal unless
further retention period is required in which we will obtain further consent from
you through notifications via the Portal or if such extended retention is
permitted by law.

Data Security
We make use of technical and physical measures such as using leading
technologies including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) / Transport Layer Security
(TLS) protocols for your use of the Portal in relation to any transmission of
personal information from you to us via the Portal. We also make use of
encryption software to safeguard any data given to us and strict administrative
and security standards are maintained to prevent unauthorized access,
disclosure, alteration and destruction. To safeguard your personal data, all
electronic storage and transmission of personal data are secured and stored
with appropriate secured storage as well as other relevant security
technologies.
Information Collected
No personally identifiable information is gathered during the browsing of the TM
Portal except for information given by you via e-mails.
Cookies
Certain websites generate ‘cookies’, which are collected by web-servers to
enable them to recognise your future visits.
The TM Portal uses only ‘non-persistent cookies’ or ‘per-session cookies’ which
serves technical purposes like switching the languages of the Portal. These
cookies do not permanently record data and they are not stored on your
computer’s hard drive. Once you close your browser, the cookie is deleted.
What Happens When I Link to Another Site?
TM Portal contains links to other websites, within our organizations and other
parties. This privacy policy applies only to our site and you should be aware
that other sites linked by the Portal may have different privacy policies and we
highly recommend that you read and understand the privacy statements of
each site.
Changes to this Policy
If this privacy policy changes in any way, it will be updated on this page.
Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are updated on the information
which is collected, how it is used and under what circumstances, if any, it is
shared with other parties.
Queries or Complaints
If you have any queries or complaints about this privacy policy or about the
Portal, you can contact us via our Feedback section.
Feedback
We welcome all feedbacks/inquiries.
In case of detailed information which the Portal may not be able to provide,
your feedback/enquiry will be sent to our relevant agency to better serve you.
